CONTACT ME

- 9310618101
- gulfam.sviim@gmail.com
- Utter Pradesh, India, 203207
- https://gulfaam.com

SOCIAL LINKS

Linkedin:https://www.linkedin.com/in/gulfamsaifi-b86a29166/

Github:https://github.com/GulfamASB

CERTIFICATES

IDST Pro 2016-02-01

SKILLS

Self Motivated

Dependable and Responsible

Problem Solving



Hindi English

Gulfaam Saifi

React.Js & Next.Js Developer

ABOUT ME

I am a React.js and Next.js Developer and I have worked in A Plus Studio Company as a post of web developer. And I have made full stack website/PWA for A Plus Studio company. and I have done my six months of internship experience from Ghoul-web Solutions as a web developer and I have good knowledge of react.js, next.js. and I have done some project like movies exploring website (full stack) with the help of Next.js, my portfolio by React.js, and Website/PWA for A Plus Studio Company Noida sector-83 A-218-219.

EDUCATION

2020-08 2023-08

Bachelors In Computer Application (BCA)

Asian School Of Business Computer Application Noida Sector-125 2019-03 2020-08 **Intermediate**

MB Inter Collage Commerce

Utter Pradesh Dadri -203207

EXPERIENCE

2022-10 2023-08

Web Developer

Ghoul Web Solutions LLP Greater Noida, Utter Preadsh 2023-09 Present

Web Developer Next.Js

A Plus Studio Noida, Utter Pradesh

PROJECTS

E Commerce Web PWA

https://aplusstudio.in

It Is The E-Commerce Website With PWA, I Used The Next.Js Programming Language With Mongodb Database It Is Full Stack Responsive Website.

Movie Exploring Web

https://65c20e5c1357070007746274--dapper-malabi-b6ad79.netlify.app/

It Is The Movies Exploring Websites, I Used The Next.Js Programming Language With NextOuth.

Portfolio Web

https://gulfaam.com

It Is My Personal Websites And It Is The Fully Responsive Website. And I Used The React. Js Programming Language For This Portfolio Website.

REFERENCE

Munshad Saifi

Senior Web Developer

Ghoul Web Solutions LLP

P: 9540956723

E: Munshadsaifi12@Gmail.Com